bundlepost.com 2013-04-23

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Quick Summary

  1. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and will only disclose your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy and/or with your explicit consent. 
  2. Third parties are not permitted to sell the information we provide to them, to market directly to you, or to disclose it in any other way without your explicit consent. 
  3. We share your personal information with Internal Service Providers for our operations only to facilitate or outsource a BundlePost.com service or operation when absolutely necessary and under confidential restrictions. 
  4. We do not share your personal information with other Bundle Post users or members. 
  5. We disclose limited personal contact information to verified requests by law enforcement and government officials who conduct criminal investigations, and require a subpoena for additional personal information, in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 
  6. We will provide you with notice if our privacy policy changes.
  7. We let you change your personal information so that you can keep it up to date.
  8. We use safe, secure technology and other privacy protection programs to keep your personal information secure on BundlePost.com.

**Detailed Privacy Policy**

**Contents**

  * Scope
  * Collection
  * Marketing
  * Use 
  * Our Disclosure of Your Information 
  * Information You Share on BundlePost.com
  * Cookies
  * No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing
  * Account Protection
  * Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information
  * Security
  * Third Parties
  * General
  * Web Beacons, Cookies & Related Tools

**Scope**

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on the BundlePost.com website. It applies generally to the BundlePost.com website and content.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on January 1, 2011. 

**Collection**

You can browse our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to sign up for a BundlePost.com account, you provide us with personal information and you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. 

We may collect and store the following personal information: 

  * email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the site (such as third-party account information and login(s), and content you generate or other activities that relates to your account); 
  * billing and other information you provide to purchase or sign up for a subscription; 
  * community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our site, and correspondence sent to us; 
  * other information from your interaction with our site, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information; 
  * additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity or ownership of your account);
  * information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to Social Resolve, LLC (exclusive owner of Bundle Post™, Bundle Post Product and BundlePost.com), we may conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law).

**Marketing**

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply indicate your preference in Bundle Post or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement. 

**Use**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms & Conditions Agreement; 
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; 
  * tell you about our services and those of our corporate family, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and 
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

**Our Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims, or determine if other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with: 

  * [Members of the Social Resolve, LLC corporate family](http://pages.ebay.com/help/policies/privacy-appendix.html#members)— to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you’ve requested their services. 
  * Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, etc.) ~~~~
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). 
  * Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, and fraud complaints. 
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.) 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

**Information You Share on BundlePost.com**

Your User ID and/or email address is necessary to log in to your account and is connected to all of your BundlePost.com activity. 

If you access the BundlePost.com site from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your User ID, activity or reminders from BundlePost.com, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you.

**Cookies**

We may use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * We may offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. 
  * We may use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status. 
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. 
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services. 

**No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing**

We do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your BundlePost.com communication preferences so we communicate to you as you prefer. To report BundlePost.com-related spam or spoof emails to BundlePost.com, please contact support for assistance. 

You may not use our technology and communication tools to send email, Twitter or any other type of spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools. If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community (via Refer-a-Friend or other tools), we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. 

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your BundlePost.com password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify BundlePost.com technical support or Social Resolve, LLC and change your password. 

**Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information**

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to BundlePost.com. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information as soon as you click to do so, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms & Conditions Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**Security**

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Third Parties**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Social Resolve, LLC does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

**General**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect immediately after they are initially posted on the site. In addition, we will notify you through BundlePost.com. If your questions are not answered online, you may contact us through technical support/customer service.
